啊！
啊。
噉我同佢講。
跟住咧，我就係。
啊，非常多謝立法會主席。
啊，今日啊，大家相信都知道咧，我首先咧係。
作禮節性拜訪咧，就係同啊。
首席法官啊，張舉能法官咧，係會面咗。
啊！我首先亦都多謝咗行政長官喺佢領導之下。
維護法治同埋司法獨立啊嘅重要性，我係絕對。
啊！多謝行政長官嘅安排啦。今朝咧，我係同佢見咗面。
啊！大家係討論咗有關啊交接嘅一啲安排事宜。
行政長官當選人李家超先生咧，喺琴日當選之後咧，馬不停蹄。
啊！昨天嘅選舉係舉辦得係相當成功，包括咧係好暢順。
咁今日亦都係啊第一時間咧，嚟到立法會啊去同我見面。咁或者而家我交畀許家騏先生啊講講先，好嘛？
啊，同埋咧啊，每一個環節都諗得好周到嘅。咁亦都多謝喺行政長官領導之下，各個參與嘅公務員以及有關人士喺攞喺呢方面做嘅一啲啊專業同埋成功嘅工作。
啊！
啊。
一向咧。
係一同去。
喺多方面咧。
立法會喺。
啊！而家喺。
啊！共同去解決問題。
係同啊政府。
啊！我亦都非常多謝立法會主席。
支持，兼且會啊配合。
我亦都同立法會主席咧，係喺度，大家係商議。
啊！司法機關喺資源方面，如果有咩需要咧？
梁君彥先生咧，今日係好客氣啊，請咗我食晏添。噉係我係係多謝。
內界嘅政府咧係會全面配合，確保啊司法機關咧可以按基本法履行佢嘅職責嘅。
啊，改善咗嘅啊，完善咗嘅選舉制度之下嘅立法會議員咧，喺立法會嘅審議工作咧係非常之啊有效率，而且好實際嘅。噉我喺啊會面嘅時候，亦係多謝咗立法會主席。
啊！
話佢有啲建議。
最高嘅。
啊，包括咧係。
禮智性拜訪。
都要保持警惕，或者係做一個鬥爭嘅心態，或者。
中聯辦啦，誒，公安公署啦。
大家喺溝通協作方面做得更好嘅，達到咧。
中央人民政府嘅四個駐港機構。
你都會考慮，想問下佢咧係啲乜嘢啦？第二就係你頭先都提過底線思維，點點解？
結果，噉啊，下晝咧，我亦都會去誒。
誒量政善治方面點可以做得更好，包括官員。
我哋喺啊，增加溝通聯繫啊，確保香港。
我哋喺完善選舉制度之下，愛國者治港原則之下咧，係令到整體嘅香港利益係達到啊！
外交部啊特派員工處以及駐軍嘅啊，噉我係啊呢個會係我今日嘅行程啊。我再次多謝梁君彥主席啊，今日同我一個好啊有用嘅溝通啊。林太有冇畀一啲建議你，譬如話加強？
作為整體嘅團隊裏邊嘅啊重要份子，點樣喺不同嘅環節咧，係可以加強同立法會員溝通，包括喺政策嘅釐定以及實際係我哋嘅政誒措施出台等等嘅環節咧，係點樣可以啊？
啊！
包括譬如。
一個穩固嘅基石。
我係會係奠定。
公共衞生風險、食物安全風險。
等香港嘅發展咧，係無後顧之憂。
當然交接裏邊咧涉及誒政府嘅架構重組嘅。
啊！大家去討論下啊交接啊嘅問題。
我係會全面評估不同方面嘅啊風險嘅。
亦都我相信一定會喺立法會討論嘅，咁所以多謝大家關心呢個問題。
啊！第一咧就我好多謝行政長官啊，今日係第一時間咧係畀機會。
第二咧，底線思維咧，就係喺我喺施政理念嗰度咧，我係講咗。
我亦都喺我嘅誒同不同嘅選委或者公眾誒溝通嘅時候咧，有提及過。
啊！呢一啲啊環節上邊，實際我嘅決定應該係點咧？所以喺呢個階段咧，就啊，我唔打算係啊將所有細節咧都公開住。但係無論點咧，最終嘅決定咧，必然會係啊公佈嘅。
政府架構嘅重組嘅方案咧，其實咧已經係做到好細節㗎。咁呢方面咧就有一啲環節咧係我有一啲睇法，咁想聽下行政長官啊佢嘅意見係乜嘅啊？我哋交流咗啦。咁因為我都會係再探討啊。
等等嘅不同領域咧，都應該作一個風險評估，誒作出有效嘅預案，確保如果真係有威脅發生嘅時候，我哋能夠誒可以好有信心咁處理嘅。呢個就係底線思維。咁簡單。
係啊！
嚟講。
同佢哋。
喺昨天我嘅。
當選之後咧，我見記者嘅時候都講咗。
如果喺一個施政部，誒喺一個政綱裏邊。
大家要認認識清楚嚇，噉啊！
就係作最壞嘅打算，而作最好嘅準備。
我嘅政綱裏邊講得好清楚，我嘅施政重點係邊啲方面嘅。
違反法律嘅自由，咁所以喺法律容許之下咧，大家係有絕對大嘅自由嘅。呢個咧，我相信咧。
言論自由、集會自由等等，基本法裏邊講得好清楚嘅自由，都係喺我哋擁有咗㗎啦。但係呢啲自由唔代表。
溝通同埋交流，聽佢哋意見，去進行我其他方面嘅工作嘅。咁所以咧，喺方方面面咧，我嘅工作咧都會好認真咁展開嘅。
誒，起碼係有篇幅上面嘅限制咧，我都解釋過，唔會每一個環節咧都會去提及嘅，唔提及嘅亦都唔表示我唔關注嘅。
我開展嘅工作咧，包括會去全力去落實我政工嘅工作，亦都同時講明，我會繼續接觸不同嘅人士或者去地區。
係咪你嘅當選宣言咧都冇提到言論自由啊、新聞自由啲核心價值？你認為係咪已經有咗，所以唔需要捍衞？你會承諾，你嘅任內呢一啲嘅自由都係不會改變。同埋你下晝去中聯辦，誒係咪一個借票嘅行程咧？你認為你攞到四票係你自己爭取嘅努力，定係有中聯辦幫你拉票咧？
香港嘅自由同埋權利咧，喺基本法裏邊充分寫曬出嚟，兼且保障咗㗎啦。就等於我答大家新聞自由，其實係我哋已經擁有咗㗎啦，已經喺我哋袋裏邊㗎啦。所以香港嘅。
subject。
also。
對，wrong。
啊！ violate。
against。
the month.
啊，That.
呢套現在我。
一 lot of you.
所以那點 has to be very clear.
我聽我聽聽英文嗰個問題啦，唔該。
first of all, I think in
我conducted my election campaign.
them their action are contravening the law. It is their action.
people are brought to court because of the suspicion.
Let me answer your first first. Okay, I think you are very wrong to describe that people are now charged simply because of their expressed opinions. That is absolutely wrong, and it should not be so described. It is misleading, and actually and factual.
嗯。
Districts.
meet people.
were with me。
呢啲開放。
to explain my。
啊，campaign。
philosophy of governance。
when I went to.
to various people.
went to.
of the election.
所以我 make my effort in the whole month.
或conduct face-to-face or online meetings.
and I remember that on one day I went around to ten places.
And a lot of your colleagues were with me, and they actually said that well, they had a long day.
and。
and I hope.
to try to explain.
to again explain my.
所以，我 make 很多努力。
how?
到社會。
and I also did a lot of online meetings with.
I hope you will also reflect.
and win the support of the people I met.
and the achievements that I want to be realised.
我 intent， the sixth government will bring。
and my colleagues in the campaign office also made a lot of efforts.
representatives of different sectors, particularly members of election committee.
when people saw all these activities and the work that we conducted tirelessly every day, then
philosophy of governance, my intention of how if I get elected, then the sixth term government would do.
被枉。
of chaos.
因為。
The election was conducted.
我唔同意，and I think they.
with a high degree of foreign intervention.
internal wastage。
所以，係我嘅個人嘅努力。
and of course I thank for the opportunities that the public has given me.
And the last thing about the comments made by the EU.
enacted because of what happened in the years.
and also attempts to sabotage Hong Kong governance.
and I'm of course very grateful to members of the election committee who voted for me.
After hearing what my intention and purposes would be in the sixth term government.
According to the election law in Hong Kong, and the election law in Hong Kong was.
this activities to people of Hong Kong so that they actually saw how hard I work and how hard my colleagues work together with me.
啊！
I think a lot of.
In。
off。
which we have now.
A lot of debates.
There is broad representation.
The two to three years leading.
Improving the electoral system.
所以，它已經已經創造。
到的 situation， that resulted。
It is an improved system in which.
所以它 was against this background, which.
positive results，as you can see，that in electrical
people saw and experienced during.
interest， and also， is in accordance with the actual situation of Hong Kong。
and。
our country.
We should stand firm.
係非常實用。
所以，我唔同意佢哋嘅comments。
A lot of the discussions.
啊，very rational and of high quality.
about the need for such an electoral system.
時間差唔多唔該曬，好啊。O.K. 多謝各位。主席轉頭上嚟再同大家見面嘅。
and that is the benefit that has been brought as a result of the electoral new electoral system.
How we run Hong Kong affairs is a matter of Hong Kong SAR, and also as a matter of
But I think people are adopting double standard when we have through our law a an improved electoral system, which is creating benefit to the people of Hong Kong.